<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Japanese News 01</title>
    <link href="/2021/04/25/Japanese-News-001/"/>
    <url>/2021/04/25/Japanese-News-001/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>安倍前首相(あべぜんしゅしょう)、動(うご)き活発化(かっぱつか)　「再々登板視野(さいさいとうばんしや)」臆測(おくそく)も</p><p>自民党(じみんとう)の安倍晋三前首相(あべしんぞうぜんしゅしょう)が動(うご)きを活発化(かっぱつか)させている。</p><p>同党(どうとう)の保守系(ほしゅけい)グル(ぐる)ープ(ぷ)や議員連盟(ぎいんれんめい)の役員(やくいん)に相次(あいつ)いで就任(しゅうにん)。首相在任中(しゅしょうざいにんちゅう)に果(は)たせなかった憲法改正(けんぽうかいせい)への熱意(ねつい)を公(おおやけ)の場(ば)で訴(うった)えている。党内(とうない)では「再々登板(さいさいとうばん)が視野(しや)にあるのでは」との臆測(おくそく)も出ている。</p><p>「新(あたら)しい薬(くすり)が大変(たいへん)よく効(き)き、あと2(２)回(かい)ぐらい点滴(てんてき)をすれば一応治療(いちおうちりょう)が終(お)わる」。安倍氏(あべし)は22(２２)日(にち)に東京都内(とうきょうとない)で開(ひら)かれた憲法(けんぽう)に関(かん)するシンポジウム(しんぽじうむ)で、首相辞任(しゅしょうじにん)の引(ひ)き金(がね)となった潰瘍性大腸炎(かいようせいだいちょうえん)の治療(ちりょう)についてこう報告(ほうこく)した。</p><p>安倍氏(あべし)は「桜(さくら)を見(み)る会(かい)」前夜祭(ぜんやさい)の問題(もんだい)を受(う)け、首相辞任後(しゅしょうじにんご)しばらくは目立(めだ)った活動(かつどう)を控(ひか)えていた。しかし今月(こんげつ)、自民保守系議員(じみんほしゅけいぎいん)でつくる二(ふた)つの議連(ぎれん)に顔(かお)を出(だ)し、それぞれ顧問(こもん)に就任(しゅうにん)。22(２２)日(にち)の議連会合(ぎれんかいごう)では「保守政党(ほしゅせいとう)として、日本(にほん)を日本(にほん)たらしめるものに、常(つね)に思いをはせながら取(と)り組(く)んでほしい」と呼(よ)び掛(か)けた。</p><p>宿願(しゅくがん)の憲法改正(けんぽうかいせい)では、党憲法改正推進本部(とうけんぽうかいせいすいしんほんぶ)の最高顧問(さいこうこもん)に就任(しゅうにん)し、同本部内(どうほんぶない)から「挙党体制(きょとうたいせい)で推進(すいしん)できる」（幹部(かんぶ)）と期待(きたい)の声(こえ)が出(で)ている。安倍氏(あべし)は22(２２)日(にち)のシンポジウム(しんぽじうむ)で、立憲民主党(りっけんみんしゅとう)の枝野幸男代表(えだのゆきおだいひょう)が安倍政権(あべせいけん)の間(あいだ)は議論(ぎろん)に応(おう)じない方針(ほうしん)だったことを引(ひ)き合(あ)いに「もう首相(しゅしょう)じゃないから議論(ぎろん)しろよと思(おも)う」と批判(ひはん)してみせた。</p><p>自民内(じみんない)には、安倍氏(あべし)の3(３)度目(どめ)の首相登板(しゅしょうとうばん)を待(ま)ち望(のぞ)む声(こえ)もあり、ベテラン(べてらん)議員(ぎいん)は「あり得(う)る話(はなし)だ」と語(かた)る。</p><p>注目(ちゅうもく)されるのは出身派閥(しゅっしんはばつ)である細田派(ほそだは)への復帰(ふっき)のタイミング(たいみんぐ)だ。派内(はない)には衆院選前(しゅういんせんまえ)の会長就任(かいちょうしゅうにん)を求(もと)める声(こえ)もある。一方(いっぽう)、同派幹部(どうはかんぶ)は、桜(さくら)を見(み)る会(かい)をめぐる事件(じけん)で元公設第(もとこうせつだい)1(１)秘書(ひしょ)への東京地検(とうきょうちけん)の再捜査(さいそうさ)を踏(ふ)まえ、「捜査(そうさ)が終(お)わるまでは難(むずか)しい」とみている。</p><p>安倍氏(あべし)の退陣後(たいじんご)、長年暗礁(ながねんあんしょう)に乗(の)り上(あ)げていた国民投票法改正案(こくみんとうひょうほうかいせいあん)の国会審議(こっかいしんぎ)は動(うご)きだした。このため、「野党(やとう)が再(ふたた)び反発(はんぱつ)しかねない。もうしばらく静(しず)かにしていてほしい」（自民中堅）と自重を求める声もある。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Japanese</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>TOPIK 01</title>
    <link href="/2021/04/25/TOPIK-001/"/>
    <url>/2021/04/25/TOPIK-001/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Economist 01</title>
    <link href="/2021/04/25/Economist-001/"/>
    <url>/2021/04/25/Economist-001/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Leaders 2021-04-24</p><p>*Russia’s president menace his people and neighbours</p><p>** The west should raise the cost of his malign behaviour</p><p>One man commands a police state. The other is locked up and close to death. Nonetheless, Vladimir Putin fears his prisoner. Alexei Navalny may be physically weak: after most of a month on hunger strike, he was moved to a prison hospital on April 19th, perhaps for force-feeding. Yet he is still Russia’s most effective opposition leader. His jocular, matter-of-fact videos resonate with voters. One, a guided tour of a gaudy palace that Mr Putin denies owning, has been viewed more than 116m times. Mr Navalny has built a movement by mocking the Kremlin’s lies, and challenges Mr Putin’s party at elections. That is why he was poisoned last year, and then jailed on bogus charges. It is why his organisation has been branded “extremist” and is being ruthlessly shut down. It may also explain why Mr Putin, eager to change the subject and fire up patriotic Russian supporters, is once again menacing the neighbours.</p><p>#弗拉基米尔·普京掌控着一个警察国家；另一个男人在牢狱里奄奄一息。然而弗拉基米尔·普京害怕他的囚徒。阿列克谢·纳瓦利内身体上的虚弱，经过将近一个月的绝食抗议，4月19日他被移送到一个监狱医院，或许会强迫进食。然而他仍然是俄罗斯最具影响力的反对派领袖。他所拍摄的戏谑但真实的视频引起其他人的共鸣。普京否认华丽宫殿的游览视频获得了1.16亿的观看量。克林姆林的谎言，质疑普京党派的选举结果。这使他以莫须有的罪名遭到了牢狱之灾。他的组织被冠上“极端分子”的头衔，遭到了残酷的打压。这也解释了为什么普京急切地改变话题，煽动爱国的俄罗斯人，再一次胁迫邻居。#</p><p>In recent weeks he has massed more than 100,000 troops on the border with Ukraine, a country he has already partly dismembered by grabbing Crimea and backing pro-Russian secessionists in the Donbas, an eastern region. Meanwhile, his navy has threatened to block the Kerch strait, cutting off parts of Ukraine from the Black Sea. On April 22nd, however, his defence minister announced that Russian forces would be pulled back again from the Ukrainian border, having completed their “exercises”. As <em>The Economist</em> went to press, it was uncertain how many troops would actually be withdrawn. In similar circumstances in the past, Russia has often left significant forces behind. Nor was it clear what point Mr Putin was trying to make with this colossal show of force. His goal may be to intimidate Ukraine’s leaders into making concessions, such as formal autonomy for the Donbas. Or he may be preparing for future aggression.</p><p>His state-of-the-nation speech on April 21st offered only the vaguest of clues. Mr Putin promised handouts for the masses and pain for his enemies. He repeated a conspiracy theory about the West trying to assassinate Alexander Lukashenko, the despot of next-door Belarus. He vowed that those who threaten Russia’s security “will regret their actions more than anything they’ve regretted in a long time”. As he spoke, his goons rounded up dissidents.</p><p>Mr Putin is weaker than he looks, but that makes him dangerous. His previous Ukrainian adventures came when the Russian economy was in trouble and his polls needed a boost. Today, his personal polls are sliding and barely a quarter of Russians support his party. Protests against Mr Navalny’s arrest in January were the largest in a decade. And events in Belarus worry Mr Putin: Mr Lukashenko has been so weakened by protests that he now depends on Russian support to stay in power. If something similar were to happen to Mr Putin, he has no one to turn to. Facing protests at home, he may lash out abroad, in Ukraine, Belarus or elsewhere.</p><p>All this poses a challenge for President Joe Biden and his allies. When deciding how to deter Mr Putin, the West should be realistic. No one wants war with a nuclear power,  sanctions are often ineffective. They rarely work if they are unilateral, or their aim is too ambitious. Even the strictest embargoes failed to dislodge lesser tyrants in Cuba and Venezuela. Russia has fashioned a siege economy, inward-looking and stagnant but hard for outsiders to throttle. Talk of an embargo on Russian oil and gas exports, meanwhile, is naive. The world must one day find alternatives to fossil fuels, but suddenly shutting off a supplier as big as Saudi Arabia would cause global economic tremors—so it won’t happen.</p><p>His state-of-the-nation speech on April 21st offered only the vaguest of clues. Mr Putin promised handouts for the masses and pain for his enemies. He repeated a conspiracy theory about the West trying to assassinate Alexander Lukashenko, the despot of next-door Belarus. He vowed that those who threaten Russia’s security “will regret their actions more than anything they’ve regretted in a long time”. As he spoke, his goons rounded up dissidents.</p><p>Mr Putin is weaker than he looks, but that makes him dangerous. His previous Ukrainian adventures came when the Russian economy was in trouble and his polls needed a boost. Today, his personal polls are sliding and barely a quarter of Russians support his party. Protests against Mr Navalny’s arrest in January were the largest in a decade. And events in Belarus worry Mr Putin: Mr Lukashenko has been so weakened by protests that he now depends on Russian support to stay in power. If something similar were to happen to Mr Putin, he has no one to turn to. Facing protests at home, he may lash out abroad, in Ukraine, Belarus or elsewhere.</p><p>All this poses a challenge for President Joe Biden and his allies. When deciding how to deter Mr Putin, the West should be realistic. No one wants war with a nuclear power, and sanctions are often ineffective. They rarely work if they are unilateral, or their aim is too ambitious. Even the strictest embargoes have failed to dislodge lesser tyrants in Cuba and Venezuela. Russia has fashioned a siege economy, inward-looking and stagnant but hard for outsiders to throttle. Talk of an embargo on Russian oil and gas exports, meanwhile, is naive. The world must one day find alternatives to fossil fuels, but suddenly shutting off a supplier as big as Saudi Arabia would cause global economic tremors—so it won’t happen.</p><p>The aim of sanctions should be modest: not regime change, but to raise the cost to Mr Putin of aggression abroad and oppression at home. Mr Biden has made a good start, imposing a raft of financial sanctions for hacking and election-meddling, which can be tightened if Mr Putin transgresses more. Harsher curbs on Western financial institutions dealing with Kremlin-linked firms would add to the pain. Mr Biden is also trying to cajole allies to present a united front, as they have so far failed to do. Germany should kill Nord Stream 2, a gas pipeline intended to bypass and squeeze Ukraine. Britain should crack down more on money-laundering. Individuals implicated in abuses should have their assets frozen and be barred from entering the West.</p><p>nato should step up. It must strike a balance: reassuring Russia’s neighbours without feeding the Kremlin’s paranoia. Some Russians imagine that nato might invade to help Ukraine recapture its lost turf. Mr Biden should make clear that it won’t. But nato should beef up its presence in the Black Sea, and its members should continue to supply Ukraine with defensive weapons.</p><p>Russia is far less important than China, either to the world economy or to climate talks. But it still matters a great deal. It is the single most prolific stoker of instability on Europe’s borders, and arguably the most energetic troublemaker in rich democracies, funding extremist parties, spreading disinformation and discord. How the West deals with it also sets a precedent. China’s leaders are certainly watching. If Mr Biden lets Russia roll over Ukraine, they may assume that Taiwan is fair game, too.</p><p>Unlike his predecessor, Mr Biden sees Mr Putin clearly. Rather than embracing him, he has called him a killer. But he also keeps communications open. He has suggested a summit. That would be a mistake if it merely boosts Mr Putin’s prestige, but not if it de-escalates military tensions and signals resolve. The diplomatic spadework that precedes it will be crucial. Fortunately, Mr Biden has hired plenty of Russia experts, and actually listens to them.</p><p>In the end it will not be outsiders who decide Russia’s future. The long, hard task of creating an alternative to Mr Putin’s misrule can be performed only by Russians themselves. Meanwhile, democracies should lend Russian democrats their moral support, just as they did in the Soviet era. Mr Biden should press hard for Mr Navalny to be released, immediately and unharmed. The world needs dissidents like him to hold the Kremlin to account. Without such checks, Russia will remain a thuggish kleptocracy, and its neighbours will never be safe.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>English</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>French 001</title>
    <link href="/2021/04/25/French-001/"/>
    <url>/2021/04/25/French-001/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>un roman</p><p>un manuel</p><p>un drapeau</p><p>un stylo</p><p>un livre</p><p>un papier</p><p>un verre</p><p>un manteau</p><p>un peigne</p><p>un disque</p><p>un velo</p><p>un magnétophone</p><p>un banc</p><p>un lac</p><p>un</p><p>une guitare</p><p>une jupe</p><p>une robe</p><p>une revue</p><p>une photo</p><p>une moto</p><p>une riviérre</p><p>une peinture</p><p>une cassette</p><p>une chaise</p><p>une </p><p>Qui est-ce</p><p>Que fait-il</p><p>Que fait-elle</p><p>Où est-il</p><p>Est-ce que c’est Marie</p><p>Qu’est-ce que c’est</p><p>C’est un roman</p><p>Ce sont des roman</p><p>Ce ne est pas un roman</p><p>Ce ne sont pas des roman</p><p>C’est le roman de Charles</p><p>C’est les roman de Charles et Marie</p><p>chercheur</p><p>acteur actrice</p><p>facture factrice</p><p>chemiste</p><p>cinéaste</p><p>styliste</p><p>journaliste</p><p>avocat</p><p>économist économiste</p><p>sectrésaire</p><p>professeur</p><p>moniteur monitrice</p><p>pilot pilote</p><p>rouge</p><p>vert verte</p><p>noir noire</p><p>jaune</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>French</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Objectives &amp; Plans</title>
    <link href="/2021/04/22/Objectives-Plans/"/>
    <url>/2021/04/22/Objectives-Plans/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Python                           (30 min/day)</p><p>French                            (30 min/day)</p><p>Korean                           (30 min/day)</p><p>Japanese                        (30 min/day)</p><p>Reading &amp; Writing        (30 min/day) (1 book/week)</p><p>Yoga / Running             (60 min/day)</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Personal</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
